Finding Aid for the Getty Research Institute Scholars Program Images and Recordings, 1985-2013 IA20026
Institutional Records and Archives
- Audio recordings, 1987-2001; Series I.; 21.7 Linear Feet (27 boxes); 1741.37 GB (944 files)
  - Scholar Year 1993-1994, Series I.H.; 282.19 GB (172 files)
    - Fifteenth-Century Flemish Portraiture, Seeries I.H.6.
      - Seidel, Linda. "Painted Promise: Art as Talisman and Testimony,", April 27, 1994; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0497a (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 2, 0497b (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 3, 0498 (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
      - Seidel, Linda. "Framework and Frameup: Reception and Deception,", May 1, 1994; (2 audiocassettes and 1 set of copies)
        - Part 1, 0509a (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 2, 0509b (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 3, 0510 (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
      - Seidel, Linda. "Giving, Getting, Begetting: The Art of Exchange,", May 4, 1994; (2 audiocassettes and 1 set of copies)
        - Part 1, 0504a (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 2, 0504b (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 3, 0505 (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
      - Seidel, Linda. "Resisting the Past: Pliny, Josephus and Franco-Flemish Art,", May 18, 1994; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0512a (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 2, 0512b (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 3, 0513a (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 4, 0513b (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
    - Lectures and presentations:, Series I.H.7.
      Materials comprise audio recordings of events, lectures, and discussions held at the Getty during the scholar year 1993/1994 that were not part of larger symposia or series within that year. The theme for the year was "The Americas." Scholars researched a very wide variety of topics related to the cultures of the Americas, from Pre-Columbian times to the present and their contributions addressed issues related to empire, colonialism, diasporas, and cultural contact, as well as the impact of these events on artistic and cultural production.
      - The Estate Project for Artists with Aids, October 13, 1993; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Part 1, 0428a (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Part 2, 0428b (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
      - Purcell, Rosamund. "Eden in a Jar: The Collector, the Curator, and the Camera,", October 25, 1993; 0429; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
      - Gutiérrez, Ramón. "The Politics of Periodization in Chicano History,", November 2, 1993; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Part 1, 0430a (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Part 2, 0430b (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
      - de Alva, J. Jorge Klor. "Black-Brown Relations: The Allure of Optimism, the Politics of Despair, and the Question of Identity,", November 30, 1993; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Part 1, 0431 (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Part 2, 0432 (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
      - Edelstein, J.M. "The Getty Center Collects,", December 2, 1993; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Part 1, 0433a (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Part 2, 0433b (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
      - The Power of the Tomb: Elite Burial and Ideology in Ancient Culture (produced in conjunction with the Fowler Museum's "Royal Tombs of Sipan" exhibit), December 4, 1993; (3 audiocassettes and 3 copies) (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Onuki, Yoshio. (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
          Digital file not found.
        - Duviols, Pierre. (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Richard. "Interpreting the Burial of an Initial Period Leader from Cardal on the Central Coast of Peru.", 0434a (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Unknown. "Beyond Burial Death Transformation and Renewal.", 0434b (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Donnan, Chris. "The Elite Burial of the Moche.", 0435a (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Calf Mendoy?, Federico. "Death in Ancient Peru and its Expression in the Seppucrows of the Amazonian Andes.", 0435b (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Discussion on the power of the tomb., 0436 (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
      - Yau, John. Excerpts from "Conversation at Midnight,", December 8, 1993; 0443; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
      - Hyde, Lewis. "'Change the Rap and Slip the Trap,' or How Hermes Makes Himself at Home,", January 11, 1994; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Part 1, 0446 (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
        - Part 2, discussion, 0447 (Box 1996.IA.02-11)
      - Sekula, Allan. "Dismal Science: Maritime Space and the Imaginary,", February 24, 1994 (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
        Digital files not found.
      - "Architects,", March 1, 1994; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
        - Fisher, Mark. Introduction to "Architects", 0457a (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
        - Houben, Francine. [Lecture on architecture: themes and composition.], 0457b (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
        - Nio, Maurice. [Lecture on his architectural projects.], 0458 (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
      - Gutierrez, Ramon. "La Persistencia de la Centralidad en Las Plazas Mayores Americanas. El Caso de Buenos Aires,", March 7, 1994; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
        - Part 1, 0459 (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
        - Part 2, 0460 (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
      - Meadow, Mark. "Aertsen's Christ in the House of Martha and Mary, Serlio's Architecture and the Meaning of Location,", March 8, 1994; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
        - Part 1, 0461 (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
        - Part 2, 0462 (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
      - Grementieri, Fabio. "Turn of the Century Architecture in Argentina: The High Game of Transliteration,", March 17, 1994; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
        - Part 1, 0466 (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
        - Part 2, 0467 (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
      - Schimmelpfennig, Bernhard. "The Known, Unknown 'Founder of California': Junipero Serra: Myth and Reality on His Native Island Mallorca,", April 5, 1994; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
        - Part 1, 0483 (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
        - Part 2, 0484 (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
      - Morse, Richard. "Urban Modernism in Sao Paulo and Buenos Aires, 1910-30 (with a note on Mexico),", April 12, 1994; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
        - Part 1, 0485a (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
        - Part 2, 0485b (Box 1996.IA.02-12)
      - Baza, Larry, Stephen Berens, Lauren Lesko, Nobuho Nagasawa, Randy Sommer, Fred Wilson and Roberto Bedoya. "On Contemporary Art: Alternatives," Panel Discussion, April 19, 1994; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 1, 0489a (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 2, 0489b (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 3, 0490 (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
      - Branham, Joan R. "Women, Blood and Boundaries in Late Antique and Early Medieval Sacred Spaces,", April 19, 1994; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 1, 0491 (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 2, 0492 (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
      - Rosenthal, Rachel and Harry Gamboa, Jr. "Connections 2: Explorations in the Getty Center Collections by Harry Gamboa, Jr., Nobuho Nagasawa, Noah Purifoy and Rachel Rosenthal,", May 17, 1994; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Rosenthal, Rachel and David Jensen. Part 1, 0511a (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Gamboa, Harry lecture and discussion. Part 2, 0511b (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
      - Loomis, John A. "Politically Incorrect? Unacknowledged Architectural Masterpieces of the Cuban Revolution,", May 23, 1994; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 1, 0514a (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 2, 0514b (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Part 3, 0515 (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
      - Nagasawa, Nobuho and Noah Purifoy. "Connections 2: Explorations in the Getty Center Collections by Harry Gamboa, Jr., Nobuho Nagasawa, Noah Purifoy and Rachel Rosenthal,", May 24, 1994; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Purifoy, Noah. Part 1, 0516a (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Nagasawa, Nobuho. Part 2, 0516b (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
        - Discussion. Part 3, 0516c (Box 1996.IA.02-13)
      - De Los Santos, Nancy, Liz Guillen, Ramon Gutierrez, Mauricio Mazon, Luis Rodriguez. "In Conversation: Being Latino,", June 1, 1994; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Part 1, 0520a (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Part 2, 0520b (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
      - de Alva, J. Jorge Klor. "Cultural Difference and Democracy: Against Cochlear Implants, the Integration of Indians and Apartheid by any Name,", June 8, 1994; (2 audiocassettes and 1 mini-tape copy) (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Part 1, 0524a (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Part 2, 0524b (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Part 3, 0525 (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
      - Leclerc, Gustavo, Daniel Martinez, Leticia Quezada, Josephine Ramirez, and Father Juan Santillan. "In Conversation: Being Latino", June 8, 1994; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Part 1, 0527 (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Part 2, 0528 (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
      - Vergara, Camilo Jose and Mike Davis, "Documenting the New American Ghetto," Work in Progress Lecture and Discussion, June 9, 1994; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Vergara, Camilo Jose. Part 1, 0529a (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Davis, Mike. Part 2, 0529b (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Discussion. Part 3, 0530 (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
      - Reese, Thomas F. "The Nuevas Poblaciones de Sierra Morena y Andalucia: Colonization and Agrarian Reform in Eighteenth-Century Spain,", June 14, 1994; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Part 1, 0533 (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Part 2, 0534 (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
      - Settis, Salvatore. "Art History as a Comparison of Cultures: Aby Warburg, the Pueblo Indians and the Nachleben der Antile, " Director's Research Seminar, June 20, 1994; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Settis, Salvatore. Part 1, 0535a (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Settis, Salvatore. Part 2, 0535b (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Discussion. Part 3, 0536 (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
      - True, Marion. "It's Who You Know that Counts: Immortalized Friends of Alexander the Great," Director's Research Seminar, June 27, 1994; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - True, Marion. Part 1, 0537a (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Discussion. Part 2, 0537b (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
  - Scholar Year 1994-1995, Series I.I.; 358.61 GB (205 files)
    Materials comprise recordings of events, lectures, and discussions held at the Getty during the scholar year 1994/1995, which was themed "Memory." The GRI extended invitations to a broad range of scholars whose work explored the subject of memory as a psychological, cultural, and historical practice. A particular focus of study was the modes in which memory is organized, whether oral, corporeal, or institutional.
    - Imaging the City in the Americas: The Formation and Display of Urban Identity around 1910, Series I.I.1.
      Materials comprise 1994-1995 recordings of the seminar "Imaging the City in the Americas." According to director Thomas F. Reese, the "research focus of the seminar is to consider how the image of the American city came into being and how it functioned in the construction of civic identities. In a multidisciplinary and comparative approach to the subject, and within the context of social, political, and economic conditions of urbanization, the seminar focuses on selected cities that experienced rapid demographic change and economic expansion in the early 20th century, in order to examine the relationship between the politics of their development and their visual representation in popular culture, art, and literature. The objective is to illuminate not only the means by which ideas and images of urban form were constructed for, as well as by, various urban constituencies, but also the full range of modernist technologies that were harnessed for these purposes."
      - Borges, Dain. "Imaging Rio: Spiritism, Spectatorship and the face of the Crowd during Carioca, Belle Epoque,", December 12, 1994; (3 audiocassettes)
        - Borges, Dain. Part 1, 0572 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 2, 0573 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 3, 0574a (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 4, 0574b (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
      - Valdez, Rafael Lopez, Stephan Palmie and David Brown. "Imaging Havana: The City's Cultural Milieu Under U.S. Occupation.", May 8, 1995; (3 audiocassettes)
        - Valdez, Rafael Lopez. Part 1, 0627a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Palmie, Stephan. Part 2, 0627b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Brown, David. Part 3, 0628 (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Discussion. Part 4, 0629 (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
      - Lambert, Phyllis, Alan Stewart and Robbert Flick. "From Fortified Town to Metropolis: A New Role for Digitized Information in Imaging and Exhibiting Montreal,", June 14, 1995; (3 audiocassettes and 1 set of copies)
        - Lambert, Phyllis. Part 1, 0651a (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Lambert, Phyllis. Part 2, 0651b (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Discussion. Part 3, 0652 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Discussion. Part 4, 0653 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
      - "The American City in the Photographer's Eye,", June 20-21, 1995; (5 audiocassettes)
        - McElroy, Keith, Luis Priamo, Boris Kossoy. part 1, June 20, 1995
          - Part 1a, 0659a (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
          - Part 1b, 0659b (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
          - Part 1c, 0660 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Hales, Peter, Alejandro Castellanos-Cadena. part 2, June 21, 1995
          - Part 2a, 0661a (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
          - Part 2b, 0661b (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
          - Part 2c, 0662 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Aleandro Castianos, part 3, June 21, 1995
          - Part 3a, 0663a (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
          - Part 3b, 0663b (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
    - Imaging the Us: An Exploration of Autobiographical Writings, Series I.I.2.
      Materials comprise recordings of a series of readings, interviews, and discussions based on the theme, "Imaging the Us." Some of the events in the series were held at the Los Angeles Central Library in April of 1995 and included participants Quincy Troupe, Dorothy Allison, Isaac Julien, Gioconda Belli, Anchee Min, and Greg Sarris, who read from their own autobiographical works and discussed the relationships among autobiographical writing, memory, and the articulation of an "Us." The second aspect of the series was a sequence of radio interviews/discussions with authors hosted by Michael Silverblatt on KCRW. This series of radio interviews, a collaboration between Bookworm and the Getty Center for the History of Art and the Humanities, centered around autobiography and collective memory within the "Imaging the Us" theme.
      - Troupe, Quincy and Isaac Julien. "Improvising Lives.", April 11, 1995; (1 audiocassette)
        - Part 1, 0612a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 2, 0612b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Belli, Giocanda and Anchee Min. "Memoirs as Social Testimony and Acts of Resistance.", April 18, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0615 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 2, 0616 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Allison, Dorothy and Greg Sarris. "Passing: Class, Race and Stories.", April 25, 1995; (1 audiocassette)
        - Part 1, 0619a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 2, 0619b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - KCRW. Imaging the Us, April 1995; (3 audiocassettes)
        - Cisneros, Sandra. Part 1, 0603a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Troupe, Quincy. Part 2, 0603b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Allende, Isabel. Part 3, 0604a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Sarris, Greg and Dorothy Allison. Part 4, 0604b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Min, Anchee. Part 5, 0605a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Galeano, Eduardo. Part 6, 0605b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
    - Ginzburg, Carlo. "Making Things Strange: The Prehistory of a Literary Device", Series I.I.3.
      The audio recordings capture lectures presented by Carlo Ginzburg in the spring of 1995 as he discusses the concept of "Making Things Strange." Ginzburg suggests that gaining perspective on some works of art is best achieved by distancing oneself from the work, and that this type of estrangement is a literary device with its own unique history.
      - Making Things Strange. Part 1, April 12, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1a, 0613a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 1b, 0613b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 1c, 0614 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Making Things Strange. Part 2, April 26, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 2a, 0620a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 2b, 0620b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 2c, 0621a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 2d, 0621b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
      - Making Things Strange. Part 3, May 3, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 3a, 0625a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 3b, 0625b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 3c, 0626 (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
      - Making Things Strange. Part 4, May 10, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 4a, 0631a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 4b, 0631b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 4c, 0632 (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
      - Making Things Strange. Part 5, May 17, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 5a, 0641a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 5b, 0641b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 5c, 0642a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 5d, 0642b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
      - Making Things Strange. Part 6, May 24, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 6a, 0643a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 6b, 0643b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 6c, 0644a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 6d, 0644b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
      - Making Things Strange. Part 7, May 31, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 7a, 0647a (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Part 7b, 0647b (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Part 7c, 0648 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
    - Lectures and presentations, Series I.I.4.
      Materials comprise audio recordings of events, lectures, and discussions held at the Getty during the scholar year 1994/1995 that were not part of larger symposia or series within that year. For the 1994/1995 year, invitations were extended to a broad range of scholars whose work explored the subject of memory as a psychological, cultural, and historical practice. A particular focus of study was the modes in which memory is organized, whether oral, corporeal, or institutional.
      - Tainter, Joseph. "Why Civilizations Collapse," Director's Research Seminar, September 20, 1994; (1 audiocassette)
        - Tainter, Joseph. Part 1, 0544a (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Discussion. Part 2, 0544b (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
      - Fredericksen, Burton. "Documents for the History of Collecting (on Disc)," Director's Research Seminar, September 20, 1994; (1 audiocassette)
        - Part 1, 0545a (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Part 2, 0545b (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
      - Lavin, Sylvia. "The Scandal of the Speaking Tree: Watelet's 'Essau sur les jardins,'" Work in Progress Lecture, September 30, 1994; 0546; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
      - Stone, Marla. "Hegemonic Pluralism: State Patronage of the Fine Arts in Fascist Italy," Work in Progress Lecture, October 14, 1994; 0547 (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
      - West, Cornel and Jorge Klor de Alva. "Black Brown Relations: Are Alliances Possible?", October 23, 1994; (2 audiocassettes and 1 set of copies)
        - Part 1, 0549a (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Part 2, 0549b (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Part 3, 0550 (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
      - Thompson, Lloyd. "Your Roman Ancestors and Mine: The Urge to Recolor Roman Antiquity," Director's Lecture Series, November 3, 1994; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0553 (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Part 2, 0554 (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
      - Howe, Eunice. "Woman's Place at the Hospital and Church of Santo Spirito in Sassia during the Renaissance," Work in Progress Lecture, November 11, 1994; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Howe, Eunice. Part 1, 0555 (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
        - Discussion. Part 2, 0556 (Box 1996.IA.02-14)
      - Pierantoni, Ruggero. "The Graphical and Pictorial Representation of Movement: Its Tricks, Triumphs and Failures," Director's Lecture Series, November 21, 1994; (1 audiocassette)
        - Pierantoni, Ruggero. Part 1, 0558a (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 2, 0558b (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
      - Maffei, Lamberto. "Visual Perception and Painting," Director's Research Seminars, November 22, 1994; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Maffei, Lamberto. Part 1, 0559 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 2, 0560 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
      - Pollini, John. "The Augustus from Prima Porta and the Transformation of the Polydeitan Heroic Ideal," Director's Research Seminars, December 1, 1994; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Pollini, John. Part 1, 0562 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 2, 0563 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
      - Revel, Jacques. "Narrative Strategies, Historical Knowledge," Director's Research Seminars, December 7, 1994; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Revel, Jacques. Part 1, 0564 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 2, 0565a (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 3, 0565b (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
      - Hobsbawm, Eric. "State, Ethnicity, Religion and Collective Identity," Director's Lecture Series, December 8, 1994; (2 audiocassettes and 1 set of copies)
        - Hobsbawm, Eric. Part 1, 0566 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 2, 0567 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
      - Ostrow, Steven F. "'The Moon, whose Orb Through Optic Glass the Tuscan artist views': Cigoli's Immaculate Virgin and Galileo's Moon," Work in Progress Lecture, December 9, 1994; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Ostrow, Steven F. Part 1, 0570 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 2, 0571 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
      - Mossetto, Gianfranco. "The Economics of Counterfeiting," Director's Research Seminar, December 13, 1994; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Mossetto, Gianfranco. Part 1, 0575 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 2, 0576 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
      - Coerver, Chad. "Imaging Adultery in the Quattrocento: The Case of Pier Maria Rossi,", January 10, 1995; 0577; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
      - Meadow, Mark. "Brueghel's Procession to Calvary, Aemulatio and the Space of Vernacular Style," Work in Progress Lecture and Discussion, January 20, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Meadow, Mark. Part 1, 0578 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 2, 0579a (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 3, 0579b (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
      - Mereweather, Charles. "Disputing the Sacred and the Dead," Director's Research Seminar, February 2, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Mereweather, Charles. Part 1, 0580a (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Mereweather, Charles. Part 2, 0580b (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 3, 0581 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
      - Muller, Heiner. A reading of recent work with Brigitte Mayer, February 7, 1995; (3 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0582a (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Part 2, 0582b (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Part 3, 0583 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Part 4, 0584 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
      - Settis, Salvatore. "An Adulteress: Giorgione and Titian," Director's Research Seminars, February 9, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Settis, Salvatore. Part 1, 0585a (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Settis, Salvatore. Part 2, 0585b (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Settis, Salvatore. Part 3, 0586a (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 4, 0586b (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
      - Ginzburg, Carlo. "The Painter and the Jester: Jean Fouquet's Portrait of Gonella, February 14, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Ginzburg, Carlo. Part 1, 0587a (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Ginzburg, Carlo. Part 2, 0587b (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
        - Discussion. Part 3, 0588 (Box 1996.IA.02-15)
      - Hess, Catherine. "The Gentili Family Archive and the Early Use of Pounced Design for Maiolica Decoration," Director's Research Seminar, February 16, 1995; (1 audiocassette)
        - Hess, Catherine. Part 1, 0589a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Discussion. Part 2, 0589b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Crawford, Margaret. "The Architecture of Everyday Life," Work in Progress Lecture, February 17, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)